Uh-huh.
Miss?
Berger.
Um...
Wagon 2600 is…
Yes?
It's gone.
Zero Zero, come in…
Hello. Can you hear me?
This is Edward Diehl.
Manager at the Network Control Center.
Who are we talking to, please?
English.
Can you speak English?
Yes, a little English.
Um, this is Clara Berger
from the control center.
Can I talk to the driver, please?
You're talking to me now.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Okay, Clara, listen to me.
This train has been hijacked.
Okay, there are over 200.
The passengers on this train,
if you do not do exactly what I say,
you will put them in danger.
Do you understand what that means?
Yes, I, I guess.
Who the devil is this?
Sorry, who am I talking to?
No questions,
just listen. Can you do that, Clara?
Yes, we are listening.
Speak to the police. There was a man
that I want. His name is
John Bailey Brown.
Yeah.
Sorry, could you repeat this, please?
John Bailey Brown.
He's in Germany.
The government know where he is.
Tell them to find him.
Clara.
Yes, I will try.
No, Clara.
You will not try.
Think of the passengers.
You will do exactly what I say.
and you will do it quickly.
And if you do that, nobody gets out.
Yes?
Yes.
We'll contact the police.
Stay there.
And please don't hurt anyone.
I hold my head up just
enough to see the sky.
And when we go, we won't go slow,
we'll put up such a night.
See exactly what you are
Just keep your head and I kiss
your fist and touch the sky
To keep the world from dying
Hello? Can I help you?
Wait, please. You can't go down there…
Looks like Mr. Nelson has
somewhere he'd rather be
What, don't forget this
What do you really believe
this picture shows us,
this statue?
Sam believes this image
places the fugitive
John Bailey Brown in Germany.
And I believe this could be anyone.
I just think it's...
Olivia, some advice.
Take heed from your predecessors
and do the
absolute bare minimum for this man.
Mr. Nelson is in a hole which
he ducked entirely for himself.
Who is this "John Bailey-Brown?"
As far as we can tell,
he's a British criminal. A fugitive.
And the guy asking for him,
the hijacker, he's British too?
Yes.
Has anyone spoken to British Intelligence?
All agencies have been alerted.
But we need to act fast.
There has been a serious threat to life.
More serious than my daughter's band
murdering Beethoven?
They are evacuating all the stations.
But it's rush hour.
Hopefully that's the worst
that happens today.
We make everyone late for work.
We're working on it.
Okay, the Chief of Police is inbound.
Let's get our house in order
before she arrives.
Miss Berger--
I don't understand.
The last signal the train went through?
Rotes Rathaus?
Yes, but then it…
…vanished.
Evacuate the U5. All trains and stations.
Now.
The rest of you. Max, the U8. Sabine?
Sabine, the U7.
And so on.
We hold all trains,
but we don't crash the whole network.
We don't want mass panic.
Sarah.
If he contacts you again, you call me.
Where are you going?
To find your disappearing train.
I actually don't know.
George.
Are you breathing again?
Rebecca's given you a drink.
Sir, isn't it his fault?
The train stopped.
Thank you, Rebecca. Very kind.
We're stumped down here, aren't we?
We're not. We're moving shortly.
It's been like five minutes.
It's been nine minutes.
You need to talk to them.
What? Me? No. No. No. No, no, no.
They're your hostages.
You're the driver. You're who
they're expected here.
This will all be a lot easier.
They're kept in the dark, okay?
Trust me.
Nothing on the Yovans socials.
Should we go ask someone?
I'm sure it's fine.
He should have updated us.
Or she, they.
So what I was thinking is,
why don't we just skip the museum and
go straight to the walking tour?
True.
Whatever.
Do you want your scarf back?
My scarf?
Mm-hmm.
I wanted you to keep it.
Thank you very much.
It's massive you.
Sir, what's he saying?
Well, that's why you should
be practicing a German.
Really?
Due to ongoing service problems,
this train is unable to
stop at all stations.
We're waiting there time on a red signal.
Currently being held at a red signal.
The course is.
We should be moving in school.
Sam, where are you?
Listen, I know you came all
the way from London,
but it took me weeks to
set this meeting up.
Just call me as soon as you can.
How did it go in Nelson?
He stood me up.
I'd have a good excuse.
There's delays all over the U-Bahn.
Terror instant of some kind.
Control, this is Wagon 2637.
What's going on?
Evacuate your train. That's an order.
And stay off this channel.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this station is closed.
This is named to the next exit.
My, daren,
this baron,
this bar office is closed.
Berlin is a great.
All right.
It's very cold, well, uh,
Berlin is a very walkable city,
and we will be back up and running later.
I doubt it.
How come?
What's going on?
I'm hearing there's a driver
in serious trouble.
On this line?
Okay, we're all set.
Let's let go in.
Okay.
Just what we're gonna do it's gonna.
What is it?
Fuck.
Bato.
It's the, um, the emergency brake alarm.
Someone pulled it.
We can't move until it's reset.
What, why did they pull the alarm?
What?
Because I skip stations.
Exactly.
Alright, your problem,
you fucking fix it.
Because if you don't get this train
moving before they find us,
then we're dead.
Hey.
Don't speak to anyone?
Okay. No, I'm serious,
okay? Just remember what I said
to the control center.
People do exactly what I
say. Nobody gets you.
is her. All right.
I speak to no one.
The most thing is the main.
Edward Diehl, network manager.
Good day.
What's happening with this train?
We have the U5 locked down and
the rest of the network is on hold.
Good.
There's only a few more stations
on the line.
There's only so far he can go, yes?
…yes.
You do know where the train is, Mr. Diehl?
This map is simplified.
In reality, down there it's…
a labyrinth.
A labyrinth.
Who has been speaking to him?
Clara Berger.
- Good day.
- Hello.
You deal with a lot of these?
It's my second week here.
Then let's hear what this guy has to say.
Hey, wait, are you seeing this one?
It's okay,
you didn't do anything more. It's okay.
Worry.
Do you want to bremser?
Emergency alarm?
Yeah, of course.
Sorry about that, come on.
Hold on, George.
Shut up.
Sir, he just told him, shut up.
Enough.
I'm not the one that pulled the alarm.
Is George's fault?
It's enough.
Move that out of the way.
Let the driver do his job.
Now.
Yes.
Uh, I'm not going to be.
Hey, Driver?
What's the hold up?
Hello?
So good mate, you just reset the alarm.
Nothing is so good mate.
Some of us have places to be.
Hey, Driver?
See, some of us have extra job.
One in 2600, this is control.
The police are here.
They're ready to talk.
Excuse me, Driver?
Is everything all right?
You're bleeding.
Sorry?
Your face?
Zero, come in.
You have a cut.
No, no. Can you me hear?
Need this?
Your cab was open.
Thank you.
What about the driver?
Can we talk to him?
Otto, are you there?
Zero, come in?
Sounds like you needed.
Zero Zero, why aren't you answering?
Give me a hand with me.
Just go ahead.
Yeah.
Wishing you a pleasant onward journey.
Sir, what is that?
What do you say?
I don't know, I do.
So, what did he say?
Zero Zero, can you hear me?
Why aren't you answering?
Go ahead.
- Which button do I press? This one?
- This one.
This is Ada Winter.
I'm head of the Bundespolice
here in Berlin.
Who am I talking to, please?
There is only one name
that is important today,
That is John Bailey Brown.
Where is he?
We will get you an answer.
In the meantime,
can you at least tell me
if the driver is okay?
Are any of the passengers injured?
I know they are fine.
Just get me what I need.
I give him my word. We will do
everything we can to locate him.
Okay, let me help you.
He's here, in Germany.
Track him down and send me proof.
If you could tell us who you are,
I'm sure we can find a very quick spot.
I need his exact location or people die.
What's he doing here?
We're driving.
Sir, you have to get to me in.
Thank you.
This is good,
right? It's what you wanted.
Yeah.
And the control center, the police,
they don't everything you ask for.
Yeah.
So why keeps threatening people?
You knew what was involved when
he took the money.
Just hope no one needs to get hurt.
Me too.
Hey? Do you send me flowers?
Flowers, no.
Flowers arrived.
Marsha Nelson, no sender.
Not me.
I thought about sending you flowers,
but...
That's not what I meant.
Wait, Marsha Nelson.
Was it Sam?
Doubt it.
You haven't spoken in months.
Well, maybe that's why you're
sending you flowers.
Maybe.
I'm thinking about you today.
I tried you earlier,
but I couldn't hear through.
No signal at the Bothy, remember?
I was sort of the point.
Right. And you're sure you're
okay up there?
I'm fine. It's really peaceful here.
It's exactly what I needed.
Time to reflect.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah. Okay. Love you.
Love you.
Mr Faber.
I got here as quickly as I could.
You almost beat me.
Look, there's clearly a UK angle here,
but it's your jurisdiction.
And as I said to your boss,
if there's any information I can share,
any insight I can provide,
well, then I'll be right here.
Wait. I'll take that.
Detective Beck.
In the toilet?
Yes.
HELLO,
MR. NELSON
John Bailey Brown hasn't been seen
since the Kingdom Airlines thing.
So he is missing?
Yes.
Might be surprised if he
ended up in Germany.
This hijacker of yours seems to disagree.
He's not my hijacker.
Oh, he's British though.
Yes, I'm afraid that doesn't
really narrow it down.
The good news is that
everyone leaves a trail.
So whoever this man is,
eventually we'll identify him.
But right now we're nowhere.
Much like your train.
Actually, maybe not.
He's heading on to the U8.
The U8? How is that possible?
Miss Berger will explain.
at Alexanderplatz?
You can't change here.
Yes, you can.
If you're a passenger, yes,
but not if you're a train.
It's an old maintenance tunnel.
It was flooded 20 years ago,
so they closed it.
The old points are just beyond Rottes
Rathouse. Exactly where the
train disappeared.
He's here.
So he's making his own route.
Where will he go next?
We need to evacuate the whole network.
Already on it. We're just moving the last
few trains out of his path.
Good.
Sorry, this isn't my specific
area of expertise,
but did you say move the
trains out of his path?
Thank you.
Excuse me, you're the last ones…
…you need to leave, please.
Thank you.
All right.
That's it. That's all of them. Thanks.
Thank you.
All station managers be advised.
Please report to Alexanderplatz
to assist with evacuation.
Copy that, Control. I can attend.
The U5, yes?
No. U8.
R.
Rang.
The thing on the U.
Yeah, we'll brief
political section
when we can.
Right, just quickly, are there any U.K.
citizens caught up in it?
Come on, you know the drug.
There must be some connection or
all you suits from
SIS want to be crammed in there together.
Okay, let's just say there are
no British victims being reported.
Okay everyone, let's get started.
Okay, Clara.
Stick to the script.
We can hear everything
between you and the train…
…and we'll step in if you need us.
Understood?
Understood.
Good.
It's a huge risk to
provoke him like this.
The mobile situation is even risk here.
This will give us control.
This will give us time.
There he is.
Good job.
What are you doing?
Seriously.
Clara, I thought we had an understanding.
We do?
What the hell are you doing?
The train in front of you is broken down.
We are trying to move it.
Let me figure out how long
the engineering team will take.
GSG9 can be on site in 15 minutes.
We send armed units down there blind.
We are risking passengers' lives.
Okay. Get GSD 9 on site.
but they do not engage until I say so.
Mr. Faber, 15 minutes.
That's how long you have to get
me something solid on the sky.
Yes, okay. Copy that.
Let's go.
We're ready.
To Alexanderplatz.
And what are we telling them?
Well, are we telling them the same
lies that we're being told?
Go on.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
Yes.
The reason for us...
...the reason for is a other...
...train blocking the line like that.
How much of this bull should do
they expect us to swallow?
It's then here also for us.
...for us further.
...their nature rebuild.
What is that?
What you mean?
That, there, that doorway.
It's nothing, it's a...
Shaltraum, the room for all these
witches and so on.
And the cameras?
Yeah.
But it leads into the station and
end up to the street.
So we could go through...
No, we're not going anywhere, Otto.
Have you got a portable radio?
Okay.
Can you keep an eye on my bike?
Gonna speak to the driver.
What? Why?
Because someone's not telling the truth.
This is the whole station from here.
Hello, Driver?
Look, you are right.
There's no one there.
You want this?
Clarie lied to me about the train.
No. Engineers are on site.
But it's going to take another
10 minutes or so.
Look, there are no engineers, are there?
Hmm? You broke our deal.
Pull Winter on.
This is Winter.
I know what you're doing.
You're gonna get people killed.
We are doing everything we can
to move the train.
Stop lying to me.
Please talk to us.
We want to help you here.
Let the passengers go.
Not till I get what I want.
We are looking into it.
Why would I listen to you when
you're not being honest with me?
Move that train.
So much for buying us time.
We can still end this.
You don't have any updates for me,
do you?
Like I said,
it's your jurisdiction. I'm just
here to support.
Hello? Why are you lying to us?
Hey!
Hello?
Why have we stopped again?
I've already announced that.
Please go back to your seat.
Wasn't that British guy
going to patch you up?
This is Polizai President and Winter.
You're right. We're keeping you
in the tunnel.
We're working on your demands,
but we cannot jeopardize the
safety of your hostages.
Hostages?
Back, check this one out.
You're so dude.
Seriously.
You just released one.
My taste is proper vintage.
Like early M&M.
You're a smart man.
Okay, don't make this any more difficult
than it needs to be.
Don't fuck with me.
Don't.
Hey, there's this getting out of hand.
Is those men you're asking for
a word or is it?
Yes, he is.
Okay, we're in a stale mate here, Winter.
Keeping me here?
This is not good.
I just want to keep everyone safe.
We'll shift that train.
I told you I can't put
any more people in danger.
That's exactly what you have done.
And when people start dying,
it will be your fault.
Two minutes from Alex.
We're two minutes out from Alexanderplatz.
Get ready.
We have a different priority now if
we stay here. We're dead.
Take this off. Take your belt off.
What are we doing?
I don't understand.
Hold it.
Why? What's in it?
What's in it?
This is madness. What are you
going to do with him?
Walter?
Do you play your part? I'll play my.
Okay?
No sudden moves.
Why? What's in there? What are you doing?
Okay, Winter,
I'm gonna send the passenger
down to the next platform.
Here's a briefcase with him.
Okay. What's in the briefcase?
If you do not shift that
train by 11 a.m.,
you will find out.
So now he's threatening to
blow up innocent civilians.
It's time to take him out.
I didn't want to escalate this.
You'll forgive me.
A particular train has left the station.
A fire,
a steady,
stand on a front of a stand of a place.
Go!
We've arrived at Alexanderplatz.
Security incident.
What did you say?
My mate just texted,
he just said he can't get on the U-band
because there's been some sort
of security incident.
He hasn't said anything else,
so I don't actually have anything
more to give you guys.
Okay.
You're all gonna head down
to the platform.
You're gonna hold this out
where it can be
seen by as many cameras as possible.
We'll be here watching you.
Can you do that, Freddy?
Hmm?
Do I have a choice?
Yeah.
If you stay here and risk
the lives of 200,
or you can go down there
and risk only your room.
What if I don't give you what you want?
I just have to make sure we're ready.
I understand you have
some important information.
Yes.
Right. Yes. Um,
I think I know someone on the train.
A UK citizen.
Friends and family has
really something for
the embassy to be dealing with.
I'm from the embassy.
Okay, well, right now,
I'm busy with the
British intelligence response.
So you already know then?
Who the hijacker is?
There's the passenger,
he has the briefcase.
You're going to kill an innocent man.
No, you are.
Move the train.
Ladies and gentlemen,
So we just let this guy go up in smoke?
Maybe we should just move the train.
A strike is our only option.
Send them in.
You can't the civilist in.
I'm sorry.
Engage.
Understood.
We've got eyes on the passenger.
No sign of the target.
If you're men take one more step into
the station and is game over.
How is he seeing this?
Do you copy?
Fall back.
Back.
Excuse me?
We are evacuating this station.
Stop.
Hold position.
Did you hear what I just said?
Who's this now?
Winter?
Well, who is that?
That's one of our station managers.
I thought we had it locked down!
Oh, you're put in people's lives at
risk. Get her out of there.
We are working on it.
Help me.
Get this off me.
Why? What's in there?
Don't move. He has a bomb!
What?
Cover him. I'll go for her.
What's it to be?
Wait, sir.
Zero, zero.
You know my name, but I don't know yours.
Don't try to negotiate with me.
It's Sam.
His name is Sam Nelson.
That's he you're talking to.
Please.
Help me.
Don't move!
Come here.
Come to me.
Please don't do this.
Sam.
What the fuck?
It's Sam, isn't it?
Are you there?
Sam, are you there?
Sam, please, we know who you are
and we can figure this out.
Come, come, come. Let's move.
Don't go.
Everyone with me. Pull back.
Are you there?
Sam, please, are you there?
Sam.
Forty-five seconds.
Help!
30 seconds.
I didn't want to do this.
What?
TECHNICAL FAULT
Take you home with me.
Put your...
I don't know.